

## **KEY EXPERTISE**

- Product development from nothing
- Data analysis
- Technological products

## **SKILLS**

RICE | AB tests | JBTD recearch | JIRA & Confluence | BI | UML | Python | SQL | Flutter | Computer Vision | API | WEB 3

## **ABOUT ME**

Launched 3 products from scratch, including own business in the field of light industry.

Applied data analysis skills and wrote cited scientific articles on polymerization of composites. Use Python in my work for data analysis and visualisation.

Worked as a Back-End developer, studying Flutter as a hobby. This helps to speak the same language with the team and correctly set tasks.

Help startups as a tracker: looking at what's going on around, and it's good for karma

## **EDUCATION**

Moscow School of Management SKOLKOVO 2020 Digital Product Management

SKOLTECH - Masters 2018 - 2020

Advanced manufacturing technologies, Information systems. Red diploma.

ETU LETI - Bachelour 2013 - 2017 Economics and Management. Innovation

#### RELECANT COURSES

JOBS TO BE DONE & GROWTH HACKING 2021 Yuri Drogan Growth Hacking

MTS TRACKERS SCHOOL 2021 Product Vision

Accelerator Sustain Tech 2021 Open University Skolkovo

# Yaroslav Nasonov

## **TECH PRODUCT OWNER**

http://yaroslav\_nasonov.t.me

yaroslav.nasonov@gmail.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

## PRODUCT OWNER AT MTS

MAY 2020 - PRESENT

Dep. of digital products and partnerships

#### **Progress:**

- Conducted a full development cycle of the portal for external developers developers.mts.ru from concept to public production
- Built the processes of publishing products on the showcase and automated the connection of partners
- Reduced partner integration time from 2 months to 2 days
- Partner integrations brought the company more than 1 billion rubles
- Automated the connection of partners of the program We know Personally and MTS Premium via <u>partners.mts.ru</u>

#### Responsibilities:

- Determining the product vision with stakeholders requirements and desires
- Tasks description in the format of stories, features and tasks
- Prioritising the backlog
- Conducting UI/UX research together with designers
- Determining the architecture of the IT system together with the team
- Guiding technical writers in content management
- Portal markup and monitoring based on Google Analytics
- Forming and testing of hypotheses

#### Stakeholders:

Connected partners/clients, Internal service providers, Dep. Information Security, Corporate API Manager, Partnership Service, Lawyers, Corporate IT Architecture, Billing and Product Catalog, Infrastructure and Networks

KANBAN team of 19 people: An, Dis, Be, Fe, QA, DevOps

## COFOUNDER OF LICA.PRO

JAN 2020 - AUG 2020

#### A platform for partnerships in the garment industry. Startup

- Implemented Agile technicians in the team
- Found a problem in the garment industry market through CustDev and JTBD research
- Developed the BE prototype of the partner platform
- We have closed 4 contracts worth more than 30 million rubles.

## DEVELOPER AT GEOMETRON

DEC 2018 - JAN 2021

### Intelligent CAD systems. Startup

- Described the algorithm, architecture and integration of the product
- Implemented an algorithm for working with a details with Flask, Numpy,
- Designed, implemented and filled the PostgreSQL database
- Assembled the system into a container